Just because you're invited, doesn't mean you're welcome.
Get Out is a mystery, thriller, horror film directed by Jordan Peele.
Chris and his girlfriend Rose go upstate to visit her parents for the weekend.
At first, Chris reads the family's overly accommodating behavior as nervous attempts to deal with their daughter's interracial relationship, but
as the weekend progresses, a series of increasingly disturbing discoveries lead him to a truth that he never could have imagined.
Chris Washington, played by Daniel Kaluuya.
Rose Armitage, played by Allison Williams.
Missy Armitage, played by Catherine Keener.
Dean Armitage, played by Bradley Whitford.
Jeremy Armitage, played by Caleb Landry Jones.
Walter, played by Marcus Henderson.
Get Out is a 2017 American psychological horror film written,
co-produced, and directed by Jordan Peele in his directorial debut.
It stars Daniel Kaluuya, Allison Williams, Lil Rel Howery, LaKeith Stanfield, Bradley
Whitford, Caleb Landry Jones, Stephen Root, Catherine Keener, and Betty Gabriel.
The plot follows a young black man (Kaluuya), who uncovers shocking secrets
when he meets the family of his white girlfriend (Williams).
Principal photography began in February 2016 in Fairhope, Alabama, then moved to
Barton Academy and the Ashland Place Historic District in Mobile, Alabama.
The entire film was shot in 23 days.
It premiered at the Sundance Film Festival on January 23, 2017, and was theatrically
released in the United States on February 24, 2017, by Universal Pictures.
The film received critical acclaim for its screenplay,
direction, acting, and social critiques.
It was a major commercial success, grossing $255 million worldwide on a $4.5 million budget, with
a net profit of $124.3 million, making it the tenth-most profitable film of 2017.
It was chosen by the National Board of Review, the American Film
Institute, and Time as one of the top ten films of the year.
It won many accolades, including the Academy Award for Best Original Screenplay for Peele at the 90th Academy
Awards, with additional nominations for Best Picture, Best Director and Best Actor (Kaluuya).
It also earned five nominations at the 23rd Critics' Choice Awards, two at the 75th Golden Globe
Awards, the 71st British Academy Film Awards and the 24th Screen Actors Guild Awards.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, externally controlled
action, manipulation, dark comedy, hypnosis.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.